<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Scarlett&#39;s Blog</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-09-09T12:21:09.958Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Scarlett</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Idealism</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/09/09/idealism/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/09/09/idealism/</id>
    <published>2021-09-09T11:44:40.692Z</published>
    <updated>2021-09-09T12:21:09.958Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now close your eyes,imagine that you are telling your parents a dream which you are really really keen on ,meanwhile, you already have a plan relating to how to accomplish it ,however,your parents are extremely grave and against or even squabble with you, they merely consider you are childish at all times,and they think you are not capable to making your dream come true, additionally, deem that your decision is definitely ridiculous and absurd. Now open your eyes, what is your feeling now? at a lose? At the mercy of your parent’s dispute?Incomprehensible? Or pessimistic?</p><span id="more"></span><p>This is what the idealist confront the problem.Take the Jack Ma for example who is the most successful businessman in China, besides, a typical idealist .When he was a teacher, he has decided to establish an unprecedented e-commerce company. But, how many people support him?In other word, how many people believe him? They insisted he is a failure since they thought he was continuously daydreaming nevertheless did not focusing on things surrounding him . Can you image how much effort he need to spend in order to realize his dream?Even though he gained his goal, as a matter of fact, if people attempted to accept him on the other hand of dissuade and bother him, Chinese commercial development at least will be ahead of time. </p><p>But you might be wondering what exactly idealism is ?According to the Oxford language dictionary,the idealism means the practice of forming or pursuing ideals, especially unrealistically.However,why do the people literally bare of respect ,moreover, frequently misunderstand the idealism?A fraction of people usually hold the perspective that the so called ‘idealism’ is people living their own fantasy world, an immature person who are afraid to face the real world, or a person who has always thought of the world in his or her imagination approximates to that kind of biased.Ahead of record, I am not a philosopher or psychologist, so my uncle who is a specialist in the philosophy field actually gives me a hand and inspires me a lot .When I asked my uncle about the beneficial idealism, he told me that While the undoubted idealism should be ‘I want to turn the world into it’ rather than ‘why don’t this world operate in my way’.Can you guys completely identify the divergence as for two different types as mention above ? The latter is paranoia which means they give up to the real world ,nonetheless, the former is virtually the idealism which represents a sense of comprise at the moment to the physical world but never give up.</p><p>If we do not respect and accept the true or responsible idealism, we will totally lose a great deal of benefits .Because,To be specific,I think these sort of idealists although have already challenged profound setback,endured the pressure,they still carry an enthusiastic and pure heart, they ever so hope the world can become better,and they are willing to make a effort on it. Christoper Columbus is a pretty appropriate example, when he firstly purposed and started to navigate in the ocean, though he faced the huge amount of the harsh environmental problem during the sailing, he persisted that he would arrive the new continent and avoid the starving, death,windstorm.In this case,He did not give up but tried his best to implement the target, and Guess what?He found the America,It goes without saying that Columbus goes after the idealistic, bringing his country a bunch of wealth and reputation. </p><p>But you might ask yourself: ‘what exactly are the benefits can idealism bring to the society’ or ‘ How can idealism affect people’s live’<br>Owing to An idealism will produce many unique and creative ideas to give it a go to make it come true, the benefits of Idealism can be defined as two separate parts -solid and mind. On one side, solid.There are more and more novel products and goods invented from people’s idea. In such way, not only people will feel quite convenient in the of daily basis, but also the economy of whole country will thrive among the world, the technology will improve rapidly as well.For instance,if Edison didn’t have the idea or aim about the filament invention, people would immerse in the darkness in the long run. On the other side,mind. You cannot touch it, you cannot feel it, but it is greatly powerful that it has the ability to improve our living-standard. Such as Malala Yousafzai, she is from Pakistan, and is known for the first youngest female that won the Nobel Prize laureate.Her idea of the increasing in female education quality is strongly effective which bring up the result of both gender share the education resources equally.</p><p>Overall, I just have two solutions toward the major problem.Firstly, we can lay a solid foundation for our education, which means our schools can hold some lecture in regard to  the idealism. Besides, telling the children being creative and trying to change in order to become better rather than avoiding the problem. Clarify a clear cognition to the idealism.Secondly, with the continuous growth of social media , as it is vast spreading,we can set up the forum or publish some essay to let the people get well known and understand the idealism gradually.</p><p>Nothing is impossible with a willing heart, I hope all you guys can respect them.If idealism doesn’t exist, our life will certainly develop in a slow motion,we do not have to become the idealist at all, but at least they do deserve to be respected    </p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Now close your eyes,imagine that you are telling your parents a dream which you are really really keen on ,meanwhile, you already have a plan relating to how to accomplish it ,however,your parents are extremely grave and against or even squabble with you, they merely consider you are childish at all times,and they think you are not capable to making your dream come true, additionally, deem that your decision is definitely ridiculous and absurd. Now open your eyes, what is your feeling now? at a lose? At the mercy of your parent’s dispute?Incomprehensible? Or pessimistic?&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Love is love</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/09/09/love-is-love/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/09/09/love-is-love/</id>
    <published>2021-09-09T11:44:40.692Z</published>
    <updated>2021-09-09T12:17:53.531Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Have your guys heard about the term LGBTQ？ It’s definitely a serious topic in question. However,as far as my first touching related to this topic be concerned,I remembered that there was a really popular novel among my classmates called Call me by your name when I was in grade 6. I had a great curiosity and wanted to give it a go. As I insisted on buying it and shared it with my mom, she reacted abnormally gravely and shouted: “Over my dead body!” The reason was simply because she thought being a member of LGBTQ community didn’t fit her ethics, and she was worried about my understanding of the values of life. I felt extremely her concern was incomprehensible, after all, I knew the general meaning of LGBTQ. Meanwhile, I certainly didn’t become the so called “that kind of people” my mom imagined anyway.</p><span id="more"></span><p>From this experience, the LBGDQ community sparked a strong interest in me. I started to learn more about them. The more I look into it, the sadder I become. I saw so many people who label this community with extremely bad words. Do you really think that’s the  correct way to treat them? Can you image how hard they need to work in order to gain the respect from other? In our history, there were people who even sacrificed their lives. Take Alan Mathison Turing for example, who invented the original computer and was worthy of the genius, however he had been forced by his government to inject Estrogen for a long time, mainly due to the the fact that his lover was a man. It goes without saying that he couldn’t bear that kind of pain, and in the end he committed suicide. Zhang Guorong is another sad example. The late famous and successful celebrity had also suffered similar pressure. He was overcome by the negative public judgement on his sexual orientation, leading to his depression. Unfortunately, he jumped out from a building, putting an end to his life.</p><p> So, I think we should respect every love choice. People fall in love and stay together because they like each other, regardless of their gender. Love is love.</p><p>Fortunately, with the continued growth of social media, I usually hold onto a positive perspective, because there are more people can speak out for the LGBTQ on a wider platform, they have published tons of articles and public welfare videos and even established a forum to motivate them.<br>But, can we stop fighting? Apparently not. The most significant factor right now is that the law of China against the LGBTQ getting married, which means they are not accepted by our country. They will still face a series of tricky problems, they would still be misunderstood, be treated with prejudice or at the mercy of rumours and malicious gossip. What’s  even worse is that they had to drop out from their company or the jobs they are really keen on. Although it sounds helpless for the LGBTQ, This is what they are most likely to encounter.</p><p>So, I have several useful suggestions to advocate for them and help them. Taking the advantage of widespread internet is quite vital and effective to conduct, such as twitter, face book, Instagram, which can make more and more people  sympathize with them.You have the right to be unsupportive, but please be respectful and do not injure them. Finally, I hope you guys can encourage and value them if they are close to you.</p><p>Because love is love, we are real people, we had the right to choose love. Do you know this month is also named pride month? People are normally celebrating and holding a parade whoever wants to can take part and act as they feel. Gender is not boundary but bias, hopefully every LBGTQ can embrace bravely, side by side, under the spectacular rainbow in pride month, regardless of gender or choice of lover.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Have your guys heard about the term LGBTQ？ It’s definitely a serious topic in question. However,as far as my first touching related to this topic be concerned,I remembered that there was a really popular novel among my classmates called Call me by your name when I was in grade 6. I had a great curiosity and wanted to give it a go. As I insisted on buying it and shared it with my mom, she reacted abnormally gravely and shouted: “Over my dead body!” The reason was simply because she thought being a member of LGBTQ community didn’t fit her ethics, and she was worried about my understanding of the values of life. I felt extremely her concern was incomprehensible, after all, I knew the general meaning of LGBTQ. Meanwhile, I certainly didn’t become the so called “that kind of people” my mom imagined anyway.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>TOEFL independent writing 1</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/09/09/TOEFL-independent-writing-1/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/09/09/TOEFL-independent-writing-1/</id>
    <published>2021-09-09T10:36:49.763Z</published>
    <updated>2021-09-12T13:54:31.598Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>11月14日<br>Do you agree or disagree with the following statement?<br>It is important for the government to provide money for beautiful things and not just for<br>practical things.<br>Use specific reasons and examples to support your answer.</p><p>Whether it is indispensable for the government to provide money for fanciable things and not just for utility things have been debating for several decades, a large majority of critics insist that mere practical infrastructure are crucial, however, I hold the thoroughly opposite perspective.</p><p>To begin with, It is irreplaceable that to construct a great deal of elegant ornamentation,especially the garden,mainly due to the fact that not only it can systematic glorify our metropolis to impel it to flatter a epitome in the municipal community, but also purify the air within the adjacent area, additionally, furnish a sense of cozy among the citizens to embellish a sort of delight in the hustle and bustle atmosphere. Given that the government dent to supervise several labors to frame the garden at the central city, as they are commanded to transplant a wide variety of categories of the vegetation, such as asters , Kikyo, Aubrieta ,pine,spruce in the garden, excavate a tremendous crack in order to form the pound when water is virtually injected, furthermore,open up some gravel paths as well as proliferate diverse uncompressed facilities.,when the flora is going to blossom as well as grow,the lake initiates to ripple with the sequential ting light,these spectacular scenes and decorations emerge a feeling of relaxation as the dwellers appreciate them,beside, the people can harvest the unrestrained consciousness when they are utilizing the playground equipment, thus, it is conducive for them to release the huge pressure and inhibit the depression arising.</p><p>Furthermore, establishing the glamorous museum is absolutely indispensable when it comes to enhance distinct types of aspects of the city , firstly, ascending the esteem for the artist and the quality of aesthetic, which can render consumers a deeper understanding of the art and broaden their horizon thoroughly when they enjoy the ingenious artifacts,on the other hand ,listen the introduction related to the striking antique with guide.Aside from that it can propel the culture communication between the diversity of countries and replenish the severe civilization divergence to boost city gradually evolves to a  comprehensive and international region with prolific unique elements. In addition, elaborating the whole metropolis to elicit more tourists, under such circumstance, enlarging the configuration and the reputation throughout the world, consequently, the escalation of thrive tourism will facilitate the economy prosperity, owing to the monstrous profits from the tickets of museum, government can also exploit the fabulous money dedicated in the technology development,accordingly, the technique will transform sophisticated progressively.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;11月14日&lt;br&gt;Do you agree or disagree with the following statement?&lt;br&gt;It is important for the government to provide money for beautiful thi</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
