<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Hexo</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-09-09T11:44:40.692Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>John Doe</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>biaoti1</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/09/09/article2/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/09/09/article2/</id>
    <published>2021-09-09T11:44:40.692Z</published>
    <updated>2021-09-09T11:44:40.692Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>wenzhang</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;wenzhang&lt;/p&gt;
</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Love is love</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/09/09/love-is-love/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/09/09/love-is-love/</id>
    <published>2021-09-09T11:44:40.692Z</published>
    <updated>2021-09-09T11:55:47.372Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Have your guys heard about the term LGBTQ？ It’s definitely a serious topic in question. However,as far as my first touching related to this topic be concerned,I remembered that there was a really popular novel among my classmates called Call me by your name when I was in grade 6. I had a great curiosity and wanted to give it a go. As I insisted on buying it and shared it with my mom, she reacted abnormally gravely and shouted: “Over my dead body!” The reason was simply because she thought being a member of LGBTQ community didn’t fit her ethics, and she was worried about my understanding of the values of life. I felt extremely her concern was incomprehensible, after all, I knew the general meaning of LGBTQ. Meanwhile, I certainly didn’t become the so called “that kind of people” my mom imagined anyway.</p><p>From this experience, the LBGDQ community sparked a strong interest in me. I started to learn more about them. The more I look into it, the sadder I become. I saw so many people who label this community with extremely bad words. Do you really think that’s the  correct way to treat them? Can you image how hard they need to work in order to gain the respect from other? In our history, there were people who even sacrificed their lives. Take Alan Mathison Turing for example, who invented the original computer and was worthy of the genius, however he had been forced by his government to inject Estrogen for a long time, mainly due to the the fact that his lover was a man. It goes without saying that he couldn’t bear that kind of pain, and in the end he committed suicide. Zhang Guorong is another sad example. The late famous and successful celebrity had also suffered similar pressure. He was overcome by the negative public judgement on his sexual orientation, leading to his depression. Unfortunately, he jumped out from a building, putting an end to his life.</p><p> So, I think we should respect every love choice. People fall in love and stay together because they like each other, regardless of their gender. Love is love.</p><p>Fortunately, with the continued growth of social media, I usually hold onto a positive perspective, because there are more people can speak out for the LGBTQ on a wider platform, they have published tons of articles and public welfare videos and even established a forum to motivate them.<br>But, can we stop fighting? Apparently not. The most significant factor right now is that the law of China against the LGBTQ getting married, which means they are not accepted by our country. They will still face a series of tricky problems, they would still be misunderstood, be treated with prejudice or at the mercy of rumours and malicious gossip. What’s  even worse is that they had to drop out from their company or the jobs they are really keen on. Although it sounds helpless for the LGBTQ, This is what they are most likely to encounter.</p><p>So, I have several useful suggestions to advocate for them and help them. Taking the advantage of widespread internet is quite vital and effective to conduct, such as twitter, face book, Instagram, which can make more and more people  sympathize with them.You have the right to be unsupportive, but please be respectful and do not injure them. Finally, I hope you guys can encourage and value them if they are close to you.</p><p>Because love is love, we are real people, we had the right to choose love. Do you know this month is also named pride month? People are normally celebrating and holding a parade whoever wants to can take part and act as they feel. Gender is not boundary but bias, hopefully every LBGTQ can embrace bravely, side by side, under the spectacular rainbow in pride month, regardless of gender or choice of lover.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Have your guys heard about the term LGBTQ？ It’s definitely a serious topic in question. However,as far as my first touching related to th</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
